<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skin Classification</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Disease1">Disorders of Pigmentation</string>
    <string name="Disease1Description">Pigmentation disorders are disturbances of human skin color. There may be a loss or reduction, which may be related to loss of melanocytes or the inability of melanocytes to produce melanin or transport melanosomes correctly.\n\nTreatment options for these conditions vary depending on the specific diagnosis, severity of the symptoms, and individual patient needs. Below is an overview of the steps involved in treating light-related diseases and disorders of pigmentation:\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating light-related diseases and disorders of pigmentation is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A dermatologist can examine the affected areas and perform tests to determine the cause of the pigmentation changes. Common diagnoses include melasma, post-inflammatory hyperpigmentation, and vitiligo.\n\nStep 2: Lifestyle Changes In many cases, lifestyle changes can help improve the appearance of the skin and reduce the severity of the symptoms. These changes may include using a broad-spectrum sunscreen daily, avoiding excessive sun exposure, wearing protective clothing, and reducing stress.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments are often the first line of treatment for light-related diseases and disorders of pigmentation. These may include topical retinoids, hydroquinone, azelaic acid, and corticosteroids. The dermatologist may also recommend prescription-strength skin lightening creams, which contain a combination of active ingredients.\n\nStep 4: Laser Therapy Laser therapy is a more advanced treatment option for light-related diseases and disorders of pigmentation. It works by using targeted beams of light to break up melanin pigment in the skin, reducing its appearance. Laser therapy may be used for conditions like melasma and post-inflammatory hyperpigmentation.\n\nStep 5: Surgical Treatments In some cases, surgical treatments may be necessary to address light-related diseases and disorders of pigmentation. For example, in cases of vitiligo, a dermatologist may recommend surgical techniques like skin grafting, micropigmentation, or blister grafting to restore the appearance of the skin.\n\nStep 6: Maintenance and Follow-up After treatment, it is important to maintain a consistent skincare routine and follow-up with your dermatologist regularly. This will help ensure the best possible outcomes and reduce the risk of recurrence. Your dermatologist may recommend ongoing topical treatments or laser therapy to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease2">Connective Tissue diseases</string>
    <string name="Disease2Description">Lupus can be difficult to diagnose because its signs and symptoms often mimic those of other ailments. The most distinctive sign of lupus — a facial rash that resembles the wings of a butterfly unfolding across both cheeks — occurs in many but not all cases of lupus.\n\n Below is an overview of the steps involved in treating lupus and other connective tissue diseases:\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating lupus and other connective tissue diseases is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A rheumatologist can perform a thorough physical exam, review the patient\'s medical history, and order laboratory tests to confirm the diagnosis. Common diagnoses in this category include lupus, rheumatoid arthritis, scleroderma, and Sjogren\'s syndrome.\n\nStep 2: Medications Medications are the mainstay of treatment for lupus and other connective tissue diseases. Treatment options may include nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) to manage pain and inflammation, corticosteroids to reduce inflammation and suppress the immune system, and disease-modifying antirheumatic drugs (DMARDs) to slow the progression of the disease.\n\nStep 3: Lifestyle Changes In addition to medications, lifestyle changes can also play an important role in managing lupus and other connective tissue diseases. These changes may include getting regular exercise, eating a healthy diet, getting enough rest, and avoiding triggers that can worsen symptoms.\n\nStep 4: Immunosuppressive Therapy For more severe cases, immunosuppressive therapy may be necessary to manage lupus and other connective tissue diseases. These treatments work by suppressing the immune system, which can help reduce inflammation and prevent damage to the body\'s tissues. Common immunosuppressive therapies include methotrexate, azathioprine, and mycophenolate mofetil.\n\nStep 5: Biologic Therapy Biologic therapy is a newer type of treatment that targets specific molecules in the immune system to control inflammation. These treatments can be effective for people who have not responded to traditional therapies. Biologics that are commonly used to treat lupus and other connective tissue diseases include rituximab and belimumab.\n\nStep 6: Surgical Intervention In some cases, surgical intervention may be necessary to manage complications of lupus and other connective tissue diseases. For example, joint replacement surgery may be necessary for people with severe joint damage, while skin grafts may be used to treat skin ulcers.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Monitoring Lupus and other connective tissue diseases require ongoing care and monitoring to manage symptoms and prevent complications. This may include regular appointments with a rheumatologist, monitoring of medication side effects, and periodic blood tests to assess disease activity.</string>
    <string name="Disease3">Acne and Rosacea</string>
    <string name="Disease3Description">Acne is a common skin condition that happens when hair follicles under the skin become clogged. Rosacea is a long-term inflammatory skin condition that causes reddened skin and a rash, usually on the nose and cheeks.Below is an overview of the steps involved in treating acne and rosacea:\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating acne and rosacea is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A dermatologist can perform a thorough physical exam and review the patient\'s medical history to confirm the diagnosis. In some cases, a skin biopsy may be necessary to rule out other conditions.\n\nStep 2: Lifestyle Changes In many cases, lifestyle changes can help improve the symptoms of acne and rosacea. These changes may include avoiding triggers like certain foods, alcohol, and hot or cold weather. Good skincare practices such as gentle cleansing, avoiding harsh soaps and scrubs, and using non-comedogenic products can also help.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments are often the first line of treatment for acne and rosacea. These may include topical antibiotics, retinoids, and azelaic acid. These treatments work by reducing inflammation and killing the bacteria that can contribute to acne and rosacea breakouts.\n\nStep 4: Oral Antibiotics For more severe cases of acne and rosacea, oral antibiotics may be necessary to manage symptoms. These medications work by reducing inflammation and killing bacteria. Common oral antibiotics used for acne and rosacea include doxycycline and minocycline.\n\nStep 5: Isotretinoin is a powerful oral medication that is used to treat severe acne that has not responded to other treatments. It works by reducing the size of the sebaceous glands in the skin and reducing the production of oil. Isotretinoin can have serious side effects and requires careful monitoring by a dermatologist.\n\nStep 6: Laser and Light Therapy Laser and light therapy can be effective for treating acne and rosacea. These treatments work by targeting the bacteria that contribute to breakouts and reducing inflammation in the skin. Common types of laser and light therapy for acne and rosacea include pulsed-dye lasers, intense pulsed light (IPL), and photodynamic therapy (PDT).\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to maintain a consistent skincare routine and follow-up with a dermatologist regularly. This will help ensure the best possible outcomes and reduce the risk of recurrence. Your dermatologist may recommend ongoing topical treatments or laser therapy to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease4">Systemic Disease</string>
    <string name="Disease4Description">Systemic means affecting the entire body, rather than a single organ or body part. For example, systemic disorders, such as high blood pressure, or systemic diseases, such as the flu, affect the entire body. An infection that is in the bloodstream is called a systemic infection.\n\nThe treatment of systemic diseases typically involves a multi-disciplinary approach and may vary depending on the specific disease. However, the following steps provide a general overview of the treatment process for systemic diseases:\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating systemic diseases is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A medical doctor may perform a thorough physical exam, review the patient\'s medical history, and order various tests and imaging studies to confirm the diagnosis.\n\nStep 2: Medical Management The medical management of systemic diseases typically involves the use of medications to control symptoms, prevent complications, and slow the progression of the disease. The type of medication prescribed will depend on the specific disease and may include corticosteroids, immunosuppressive agents, biologics, or other medications.\n\nStep 3: Lifestyle Changes In many cases, lifestyle changes can help manage the symptoms and improve the overall health of people with systemic diseases. These changes may include dietary modifications, regular exercise, stress reduction techniques, and smoking cessation.\n\nStep 4: Rehabilitation and Physical Therapy Systemic diseases can often cause functional limitations and disabilities. Rehabilitation and physical therapy can help improve mobility, strength, and function, as well as manage pain and fatigue. Rehabilitation specialists may work with patients to develop individualized treatment plans.\n\nStep 5: Surgical Intervention In some cases, surgical intervention may be necessary to manage complications or improve quality of life for people with systemic diseases. Surgery may involve removing damaged tissue, repairing or replacing damaged organs, or correcting deformities.\n\nStep 6: Supportive Care Supportive care can help people with systemic diseases manage the emotional and social impact of their condition. This may include counseling, support groups, and palliative care.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Management and Monitoring Systemic diseases are often chronic conditions that require ongoing management and monitoring. Patients may require regular follow-up appointments with their medical team to assess their progress and adjust their treatment plan as needed. Close monitoring can help detect and manage any complications that may arise over time.</string>
    <string name="Disease5">Poison Ivy(Contact Dermatitis)</string>
    <string name="Disease5Description">Poison ivy is an allergic contact dermatitis that causes a very itchy rash caused by exposure to the oil urushiol, which coats the leaves of poison ivy plants. An itchy, red rash and multiple blisters develop in the area where the plant came in contact with the skin.Below is an overview of the steps involved in treating poison ivy and other contact dermatitis:\n\nStep 1: Identification and Avoidance of Triggers The first step in treating contact dermatitis is to identify the triggering substance and avoid further exposure. In the case of poison ivy, this may involve identifying and avoiding contact with the plant.\n\nStep 2: Cleaning and Cooling the Affected Area After exposure to the triggering substance, it\'s important to wash the affected area thoroughly with soap and water to remove any residual oils. Applying cool compresses to the affected area can help reduce inflammation and itching.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments can help reduce inflammation and itching associated with contact dermatitis. These may include over-the-counter hydrocortisone creams, calamine lotion, or prescription-strength topical steroids.\n\nStep 4: Oral Medications For more severe cases of contact dermatitis, oral medications may be necessary to manage symptoms. These may include oral corticosteroids to reduce inflammation and itching or antihistamines to reduce itching and promote sleep.\n\nStep 5: Prevention of Secondary Infection Scratching the affected area can increase the risk of secondary infection. Keeping the affected area clean and dry and avoiding scratching can help prevent infection. In some cases, antibiotics may be necessary to treat a secondary bacterial infection.\n\nStep 6: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to maintain a consistent skincare routine and follow-up with a healthcare provider regularly. This will help ensure the best possible outcomes and reduce the risk of recurrence. Your healthcare provider may recommend ongoing topical treatments to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease6">Vascular Tumors</string>
    <string name="Disease6Description">A vascular tumor is a tumor of vascular origin; a soft tissue growth that can be either benign or malignant, formed from blood vessels or lymph vessels. Examples of vascular tumors include hemangiomas, lymphangiomas, hemangioendotheliomas, Kaposi sarcomas, angiosarcomas, and hemangioblastomas.The treatment of vascular tumors typically involves a multi-disciplinary approach and may vary depending on the specific type and location of the tumor. Below are the general steps involved in treating vascular tumors:\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating vascular tumors is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A medical doctor may perform a physical exam, review the patient\'s medical history, and order various imaging studies to confirm the diagnosis.\n\nStep 2: Medical Management The medical management of vascular tumors typically involves the use of medications to control symptoms, prevent complications, and shrink the tumor. The type of medication prescribed will depend on the specific type and location of the tumor and may include corticosteroids, chemotherapy, targeted therapy, or other medications.\n\nStep 3: Interventional Radiology Interventional radiology techniques may be used to treat vascular tumors without the need for surgery. These techniques include embolization, in which a substance is injected into the blood vessels to block blood flow to the tumor, and radiofrequency ablation, which uses high-frequency energy to destroy the tumor.\n\nStep 4: Surgical Intervention Surgery may be necessary to remove the tumor, especially if it is large or causing significant symptoms or complications. The type of surgery performed will depend on the location and size of the tumor and may include open surgery or minimally invasive techniques.\n\nStep 5: Radiation Therapy Radiation therapy may be used to shrink the tumor or prevent its recurrence. This treatment involves the use of high-energy radiation to destroy cancer cells.\n\nStep 6: Supportive Care Supportive care can help people with vascular tumors manage the emotional and social impact of their condition. This may include counseling, support groups, and palliative care.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Management and Monitoring Vascular tumors can often recur or metastasize, so ongoing monitoring is essential. Patients may require regular follow-up appointments with their medical team to assess their progress and adjust their treatment plan as needed. Close monitoring can help detect and manage any complications that may arise over time.</string>
    <string name="Disease7">Urticaria (Hives)</string>
    <string name="Disease7Description">Hives — also called urticaria (ur-tih-KAR-e-uh) — is a skin reaction that causes itchy welts. Chronic hives are welts that last for more than six weeks and return often over months or years. Often, the cause of chronic hives isn\'t clear.The treatment of urticaria involves identifying the underlying cause and providing symptomatic relief. Below are the general steps involved in treating urticaria:\n\nStep 1: Identification and Avoidance of Triggers The first step in treating urticaria is to identify and avoid any triggers that may be causing the condition. Common triggers include certain foods, medications, insect bites, and environmental factors.\n\nStep 2: Antihistamines Antihistamines are the mainstay of treatment for urticaria. They work by blocking the release of histamine, which is a chemical that is responsible for causing the itching, swelling, and redness associated with hives. Antihistamines can be purchased over-the-counter or prescribed by a healthcare provider.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments can provide symptomatic relief by reducing itching and inflammation. These may include over-the-counter creams or ointments containing calamine or menthol.\n\nStep 4: Oral Corticosteroids For more severe cases of urticaria, oral corticosteroids may be necessary to control symptoms. These medications work by reducing inflammation and suppressing the immune system.\n\nStep 5: Immune-Suppressing Drugs In some cases, immune-suppressing drugs such as cyclosporine or omalizumab may be prescribed to control symptoms of chronic urticaria. These medications work by suppressing the immune system to prevent the release of histamine.\n\nStep 6: Prevention of Secondary Infection Scratching the affected area can increase the risk of secondary infection. Keeping the affected area clean and dry and avoiding scratching can help prevent infection. In some cases, antibiotics may be necessary to treat a secondary bacterial infection.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to maintain a consistent skincare routine and follow-up with a healthcare provider regularly. This will help ensure the best possible outcomes and reduce the risk of recurrence. Your healthcare provider may recommend ongoing antihistamine treatment to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease8">Atopic Dermatitis</string>
    <string name="Disease8Description">Atopic dermatitis, often referred to as eczema, is a chronic (long-lasting) disease that causes inflammation, redness, and irritation of the skin. It is a common condition that usually begins in childhood; however, anyone can get the disease at any age.\n\n The treatment of atopic dermatitis aims to relieve symptoms and improve the quality of life of individuals affected. Below are the general steps involved in treating atopic dermatitis:\n\nStep 1: Moisturization The first step in treating atopic dermatitis is to keep the skin moisturized. This involves applying a thick, fragrance-free moisturizer at least twice a day. Moisturizers help to repair the skin barrier and prevent further dryness and irritation.\n\nStep 2: Topical Corticosteroids For moderate to severe cases of atopic dermatitis, topical corticosteroids may be prescribed. These medications help to reduce inflammation, relieve itching, and promote healing. They are available in different strengths, and the choice of strength depends on the severity of the condition and the age of the patient.\n\nStep 3: Topical Calcineurin Inhibitors Topical calcineurin inhibitors are another option for treating atopic dermatitis. These medications work by suppressing the immune system and reducing inflammation. They are often used in sensitive areas, such as the face or groin.\n\nStep 4: Wet Wrap Therapy Wet wrap therapy involves applying a damp layer of clothing or bandages over the affected area. This helps to lock in moisture and medication, reduce itching, and soothe the skin. Wet wrap therapy should only be used under the guidance of a healthcare provider.\n\nStep 5: Light Therapy Light therapy, also known as phototherapy, uses ultraviolet light to reduce inflammation and improve skin barrier function. This treatment is often used in severe cases of atopic dermatitis that do not respond to other treatments.\n\nStep 6: Systemic Medications Systemic medications may be necessary for severe cases of atopic dermatitis that do not respond to other treatments. These medications, such as cyclosporine or methotrexate, work by suppressing the immune system.\n\nStep 7: Avoidance of Triggers Identifying and avoiding triggers that can cause or exacerbate atopic dermatitis is an important part of treatment. Common triggers include certain foods, environmental factors, and stress.\n\nStep 8: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to maintain a consistent skincare routine and follow-up with a healthcare provider regularly. This will help ensure the best possible outcomes and reduce the risk of recurrence. Your healthcare provider may recommend ongoing medication or other therapies to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease9">Bullous Disease</string>
    <string name="Disease9Description">Bullous pemphigoid is a rare skin condition that mainly affects older people. It usually starts with an itchy, raised rash. As the condition develops, large blisters can form on the skin. It may last a few years and sometimes causes serious problems, but treatment can help manage the condition in most cases.\n\nTreatment for bullous diseases aims to control symptoms, prevent infection, and promote healing. Below are the general steps involved in treating bullous diseases:\n\nStep 1: Identifying and Avoiding Triggers The first step in treating bullous diseases is to identify and avoid triggers that can cause or exacerbate the condition. Common triggers include exposure to sunlight, certain medications, and underlying medical conditions.\n\nStep 2: Topical Medications For mild cases of bullous diseases, topical medications may be prescribed. These medications help to reduce inflammation, relieve itching, and promote healing. Examples of topical medications include corticosteroids and topical calcineurin inhibitors.\n\nStep 3: Systemic Medications For moderate to severe cases of bullous diseases, systemic medications may be necessary. These medications are taken orally or injected and work by suppressing the immune system. Examples of systemic medications include corticosteroids, immunosuppressants, and biologics.\n\nStep 4: Wound Care Proper wound care is essential for preventing infection and promoting healing of blisters or bullae. This involves keeping the affected area clean and dry, applying topical antibiotics or antiseptics, and covering the area with sterile dressings.\n\nStep 5: Pain Management Bullous diseases can be painful, and pain management is an important part of treatment. Over-the-counter pain relievers such as acetaminophen or ibuprofen may be recommended, or prescription pain medication may be necessary.\n\nStep 6: Monitoring for Complications Bullous diseases can lead to complications such as infection, scarring, or permanent skin damage. It\'s important to monitor the affected area for signs of infection such as redness, swelling, or drainage, and to seek medical attention if these occur.\n\nStep 7: Lifestyle Modifications Certain lifestyle modifications can help to manage symptoms and prevent flare-ups of bullous diseases. These include wearing protective clothing, avoiding exposure to triggers, and maintaining a healthy lifestyle with a balanced diet and regular exercise.\n\nStep 8: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, ongoing care and maintenance are important to prevent recurrence of bullous diseases. This may involve regular follow-up appointments with a healthcare provider, ongoing medication, and lifestyle modifications.</string>
    <string name="Disease10">Hair Loss (Allopecia)</string>
    <string name="Disease10Description">Alopecia areata is a type of hair loss that occurs when your immune system mistakenly attacks hair follicles, which is where hair growth begins. The damage to the follicle is usually not permanent. Experts do not know why the immune system attacks the follicles. Alopecia areata is most common in people younger than 20, but children and adults of any age may be affected. Women and men are affected equally.Treatment for hair loss aims to identify the underlying cause, promote hair regrowth, and manage symptoms. Here are the general steps involved in treating hair loss:\n\nStep 1: Diagnosis The first step in treating hair loss is to diagnose the underlying cause. This may involve a physical examination, blood tests, and a scalp biopsy. Common causes of hair loss include genetics, hormonal imbalances, autoimmune disorders, and certain medications.\n\nStep 2: Topical Medications For some types of hair loss, topical medications may be prescribed. These medications are applied directly to the scalp and work by stimulating hair growth or reducing inflammation. Examples of topical medications include minoxidil and corticosteroids.\n\nStep 3: Oral Medications For more severe cases of hair loss, oral medications may be necessary. These medications are taken by mouth and work by suppressing the immune system or promoting hair growth. Examples of oral medications include finasteride, cyclosporine, and biotin supplements.\n\nStep 4: Hair Transplantation In some cases, hair transplantation may be an option for restoring hair growth. This involves taking hair follicles from one area of the scalp and transplanting them to areas of the scalp where hair is thinning or absent.\n\nStep 5: Wigs or Hairpieces For individuals who do not wish to undergo medical treatment or hair transplantation, wigs or hairpieces may be a suitable option. These can be custom-made to match the individual\'s natural hair color and texture and can provide a natural-looking solution.\n\nStep 6: Lifestyle Modifications Certain lifestyle modifications may help to prevent hair loss and promote hair regrowth. These include eating a balanced diet rich in nutrients, avoiding harsh hair treatments such as perms or coloring, and reducing stress levels.\n\nStep 7: Support Groups and Counseling Hair loss can be a challenging experience, and support groups or counseling may be beneficial for individuals struggling with the emotional effects of hair loss. These resources can provide a safe and supportive space to discuss concerns and receive guidance.\n\nStep 8: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, ongoing care and maintenance are important to maintain hair regrowth and prevent further hair loss. This may involve regular follow-up appointments with a healthcare provider, ongoing medication, and lifestyle modifications. </string>
    <string name="Disease11">Fungal Infections (tinea ringworm, candidasis)</string>
    <string name="Disease11Description">ringworm is a dermatophyte," says Weinberg. A dermatophyte is simply a type of fungi that can cause skin, hair, or nail infections."Candida is a yeast," says Weinberg. These fungi can cause infections on many areas of the body.\n\nTreatment for these infections typically involves managing symptoms, addressing the underlying cause, and preventing further infections. Here are the general steps involved in treating fungal infections:\n\nStep 1: Diagnosis The first step in treating a fungal infection is to diagnose the specific type of infection. This may involve a physical examination, skin biopsy, and fungal culture. Common types of fungal infections include tinea (ringworm), candidiasis, and athlete's foot.\n\nStep 2: Topical Antifungal Medications For mild to moderate fungal infections, topical antifungal medications may be prescribed. These medications are applied directly to the affected area and work by killing or preventing the growth of fungal cells. Examples of topical antifungal medications include clotrimazole, miconazole, and terbinafine.\n\nStep 3: Oral Antifungal Medications For more severe or widespread fungal infections, oral antifungal medications may be necessary. These medications are taken by mouth and work by killing or preventing the growth of fungal cells throughout the body. Examples of oral antifungal medications include fluconazole, itraconazole, and griseofulvin.\n\nStep 4: Management of Symptoms In addition to medication, managing symptoms can help to improve comfort and prevent the spread of infection. This may involve keeping the affected area clean and dry, using antifungal powders or creams, and avoiding tight-fitting clothing.\n\nStep 5: Prevention Preventing further fungal infections is an important aspect of treatment. This may involve practicing good hygiene, avoiding sharing personal items such as towels or combs, wearing breathable clothing, and keeping the skin dry.\n\nStep 6: Lifestyle Modifications Certain lifestyle modifications may also help to prevent fungal infections. These include maintaining a healthy diet and exercise routine, reducing stress levels, and avoiding exposure to environments that are prone to fungal growth.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, ongoing care and maintenance may be necessary to prevent recurrence of the infection. This may involve regular follow-up appointments with a healthcare provider, continued use of antifungal medication or topical treatments, and lifestyle modifications.</string>
    <string name="Disease12">papulo-squamous diseases</string>
    <string name="Disease12Description">Psoriasis and lichen planus are skin conditions that share some features in common, like a red and scaly look, but they also have key differences.Psoriasis tends to thicken into patches and can last for years or decades. You will need to manage your symptoms with your doctor.Lichen planus may stop with simple red bumps that often go away on their own, though they sometimes return. And unlike psoriasis, lichen planus can affect the inside of your mouth.You can\'t spread either condition to someone else.\n\nTreatment for these conditions typically involves managing symptoms, reducing inflammation, and preventing further outbreaks. Here are the general steps involved in treating these conditions:\n\nStep 1: Diagnosis The first step in treating a chronic inflammatory skin condition is to diagnose the specific type of condition. This may involve a physical examination, skin biopsy, and blood tests. Common conditions in this category include psoriasis, lichen planus, and eczema.\n\nStep 2: Topical Medications For mild to moderate symptoms, topical medications may be prescribed. These medications are applied directly to the affected area and work by reducing inflammation, itching, and other symptoms. Examples of topical medications include corticosteroids, calcineurin inhibitors, and retinoids.\n\nStep 3: Phototherapy For more severe symptoms or widespread lesions, phototherapy may be recommended. This involves exposing the affected skin to controlled amounts of ultraviolet light, which can help to reduce inflammation and other symptoms.\n\nStep 4: Systemic Medications In some cases, systemic medications may be necessary to control symptoms. These medications are taken orally or by injection and work by targeting the immune system or reducing inflammation throughout the body. Examples of systemic medications include methotrexate, cyclosporine, and biologic agents.\n\nStep 5: Lifestyle Modifications Certain lifestyle modifications may also help to manage symptoms and prevent further outbreaks. This may involve avoiding triggers that can worsen symptoms, such as stress, alcohol, and certain medications. Maintaining a healthy diet and exercise routine may also be beneficial.\n\nStep 6: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, ongoing care and maintenance may be necessary to prevent recurrence of symptoms. This may involve regular follow-up appointments with a healthcare provider, continued use of medications or topical treatments, and lifestyle modifications. In some cases, support groups or counseling may also be helpful for coping with the emotional impact of chronic skin conditions.</string>
    <string name="Disease13">Melanoma Skin Cancer</string>
    <string name="Disease13Description">Melanoma, the most serious type of skin cancer, develops in the cells (melanocytes) that produce melanin — the pigment that gives your skin its color. Melanoma can also form in your eyes and, rarely, inside your body, such as in your nose or throat.Nevi and moles are both types of skin growths, and while they are typically benign, they can occasionally become cancerous.\n\nEarly detection and treatment of melanoma are crucial for a positive outcome, so it\'s important to be aware of the signs and symptoms and to seek medical attention if you notice anything unusual.\n\nHere are the steps for diagnosing and treating melanoma, nevi, and moles:\n\nStep 1: Self-Examination Regular self-examination of your skin can help you detect any unusual changes early on. You should examine your entire body, including your scalp, underarms, and genital area. Look for any new or changing moles, freckles, or spots, and note their size, shape, and color.\n\nStep 2: Medical Examination If you notice anything unusual during your self-examination, it\'s important to see a dermatologist for a more thorough examination. Your dermatologist will examine your skin and may use a dermatoscope, a specialized tool that allows them to see the structure of your skin, to examine any suspicious spots more closely.\n\nStep 3: Biopsy If your dermatologist suspects that a spot on your skin may be cancerous, they will perform a biopsy. A biopsy involves removing a small sample of skin tissue from the affected area and sending it to a lab for analysis. The lab will determine whether the sample is cancerous and, if so, what type of skin cancer it is.\n\nStep 4: Treatment The treatment for melanoma, nevi, and moles depends on the size, location, and stage of the cancer. Treatment options may include:\n\nSurgery: If the cancerous area is small, your dermatologist may remove it with a surgical procedure. This may involve cutting out the cancerous tissue and some surrounding healthy tissue to ensure that all of the cancer cells are removed.\n\nRadiation therapy: This involves using high-energy rays to kill cancer cells. It may be used as a primary treatment for melanoma in some cases or as an adjuvant therapy after surgery to kill any remaining cancer cells.\n\nImmunotherapy: This involves using drugs that help your immune system recognize and attack cancer cells. It may be used in advanced cases of melanoma that have spread to other parts of the body.\n\nChemotherapy: This involves using drugs to kill cancer cells. It may be used in advanced cases of melanoma that have spread to other parts of the body.\n\nStep 5: Follow-Up After treatment, it\'s important to continue to see your dermatologist for regular checkups to ensure that the cancer has not returned. Your dermatologist will examine your skin and may perform additional biopsies if they notice any suspicious changes. They may also recommend additional imaging tests, such as X-rays or CT scans, to check for any signs of cancer in other parts of your body.</string>
    <string name="Disease14">Nail Fungus</string>
    <string name="Disease14Description">Nail fungus is a common infection of the nail. It begins as a white or yellow-brown spot under the tip of your fingernail or toenail. As the fungal infection goes deeper, the nail may discolor, thicken and crumble at the edge. Nail fungus can affect several nails.\n\nSymptoms of nail diseases may include thickened, discolored, or brittle nails, as well as pain, itching, or inflammation around the nail.\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating any nail condition is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A dermatologist can perform a physical exam and may also take a nail sample for laboratory testing to confirm the diagnosis.\n\nStep 2: Lifestyle Changes In many cases, lifestyle changes can help improve the symptoms of nail diseases. These may include keeping the nails clean and dry, wearing shoes that fit well and allow the feet to breathe, and avoiding walking barefoot in public areas like locker rooms and pools.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments are often the first line of treatment for mild to moderate cases of nail fungus or other nail diseases. These may include antifungal nail polishes or creams, as well as topical steroids or other medications to manage inflammation and itching.\n\nStep 4: Oral Medications For more severe cases of nail fungus or other nail diseases, oral medications may be necessary to manage symptoms. These may include oral antifungal medications, which can take several months to be effective, or antibiotics to treat bacterial infections.\n\nStep 5: Laser Therapy Laser therapy is a newer type of treatment that can be effective for certain types of nail diseases, particularly nail fungus. This involves using a specialized laser to target and destroy the fungi that are causing the infection.\n\nStep 6: Surgery In rare cases, surgery may be necessary to remove the affected nail or nail bed. This is generally only done if other treatments have been unsuccessful or if the condition is causing significant pain or discomfort.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to maintain good nail hygiene and follow-up with a dermatologist regularly. This can help prevent recurrence of the condition and ensure the best possible outcomes. Your dermatologist may recommend ongoing topical or oral treatments, as well as lifestyle changes, to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease15">Scabies Lyme Disease</string>
    <string name="Disease15Description">Scabies is a common contagious skin condition caused by the human itch mite. Mites burrow into the top layer of skin, where they feed and live.Scabies typically causes intense itching, which can be worse at night and potentially so persistent that it keeps you from sleeping.\n\nSymptoms of these conditions may include itching, redness, inflammation, and in some cases, fever or fatigue.\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating any infestation or bite is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A dermatologist can perform a physical exam and may also take a skin sample or order blood tests to confirm the diagnosis.\n\nStep 2: Elimination of the Source The next step in treating infestations and bites is to eliminate the source of the problem. This may involve removing ticks, washing bedding and clothing in hot water, or using insecticides to kill bed bugs or fleas.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments can be effective for managing symptoms of scabies, such as itching and inflammation. These may include prescription-strength creams or lotions containing permethrin or sulfur. For Lyme disease, antibiotics are generally the first line of treatment.\n\nStep 4: Oral Medications In some cases, oral medications may be necessary to manage symptoms of scabies, Lyme disease, or other infestations and bites. These may include antihistamines to reduce itching or pain, or antibiotics to treat bacterial infections.\n\nStep 5: Supportive Care In addition to medication, supportive care can be helpful for managing symptoms of infestations and bites. This may include applying cool compresses to the affected area, taking over-the-counter pain relievers, or using topical creams or ointments to soothe the skin.\n\nStep 6: Preventative Measures To prevent future infestations and bites, it\'s important to take preventative measures. These may include using insect repellent, wearing protective clothing when outdoors, and regularly checking for ticks or other insects.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to follow-up with a dermatologist or other healthcare provider regularly to ensure that symptoms are improving and to prevent recurrence. Your provider may recommend ongoing topical or oral treatments, as well as lifestyle changes, to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease16">Eczema</string>
    <string name="Disease16Description">Eczema is a condition in which patches of skin become inflamed, itchy, cracked, and rough. Some types can also cause blisters. Home remedies and medical treatment can help manage and prevent flares.\n\nBelow is an overview of the steps involved in treating eczema:\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis\nThe first step in treating eczema is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A dermatologist can perform a thorough physical exam and review the patient\'s medical history to confirm the diagnosis. In some cases, a skin biopsy may be necessary to rule out other conditions.\n\nStep 2: Lifestyle Changes\nIn many cases, lifestyle changes can help improve the symptoms of eczema. These changes may include avoiding triggers like certain fabrics, soaps, and detergents. Good skincare practices such as regular moisturization, avoiding hot showers, and minimizing scratching can also help.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments\nTopical treatments are often the first line of treatment for eczema. These may include emollients or moisturizers to soothe and hydrate the skin, topical corticosteroids to reduce inflammation and itching, and topical calcineurin inhibitors to reduce inflammation and itching.\n\nStep 4: Oral Medications\nFor more severe cases of eczema, oral medications may be necessary to manage symptoms. These may include oral corticosteroids to reduce inflammation, oral antibiotics to treat infections, and oral antihistamines to reduce itching.\n\nStep 5: Biologic Therapy\nBiologic therapy is a newer type of treatment that targets specific molecules in the immune system to control inflammation. These treatments can be effective for people who have not responded to traditional therapies. Biologics that are commonly used to treat eczema include dupilumab.\n\nStep 6: Wet Wraps\nWet wraps can be effective for managing eczema symptoms in certain cases. This involves applying a moisturizer or medication to the skin, wrapping the affected area in damp bandages, and covering with dry bandages. Wet wraps can help soothe the skin and reduce itching.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance\nAfter treatment, it\'s important to maintain a consistent skincare routine and follow-up with a dermatologist regularly. This will help ensure the best possible outcomes and reduce the risk of recurrence. Your dermatologist may recommend ongoing topical treatments to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease17">Drug Eruptions</string>
    <string name="Disease17Description">Exanthem is a medical term that describes a widespread rash. A viral exanthem rash accompanies a viral infection. It causes spots, bumps or blotches on your skin. You also might experience additional viral symptoms such as fever, fatigue and body aches.\n\nSymptoms of these conditions may include itching, redness, inflammation, and in some cases, fever or fatigue.\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating exanthems and drug eruptions is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. A dermatologist can perform a physical exam and may also take a skin sample or order blood tests to confirm the diagnosis.\n\nStep 2: Discontinuation of Medication If a drug eruption is suspected, the first step is to discontinue the medication that may be causing the reaction. It\'s important to talk to your healthcare provider before stopping any medication.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments can be effective for managing symptoms of exanthems and drug eruptions. These may include creams or lotions containing hydrocortisone or other anti-inflammatory agents to reduce itching and inflammation.\n\nStep 4: Oral Medications In some cases, oral medications may be necessary to manage symptoms of exanthems and drug eruptions. These may include antihistamines to reduce itching or pain, or corticosteroids to reduce inflammation.\n\nStep 5: Supportive Care In addition to medication, supportive care can be helpful for managing symptoms of exanthems and drug eruptions. This may include applying cool compresses to the affected area, taking over-the-counter pain relievers, or using topical creams or ointments to soothe the skin.\n\nStep 6: Identifying Alternative Medications If a drug eruption is suspected, it may be necessary to identify alternative medications that can be used to manage the underlying condition. Your healthcare provider can help you identify alternative medications and discuss potential risks and benefits.\n\nStep 7: Ongoing Care and Maintenance After treatment, it\'s important to follow-up with a dermatologist or other healthcare provider regularly to ensure that symptoms are improving and to prevent recurrence. Your provider may recommend ongoing topical or oral treatments, as well as lifestyle changes, to maintain the results achieved during treatment.</string>
    <string name="Disease18">Viral infection and STDS</string>
    <string name="Disease18Description">Human papillomavirus (HPV) and herpes are both common viruses that can be transmitted sexually. HPV spreads through skin-to-skin contact with a person who has the infection, including vaginal, anal, or oral sex, HSV spreads through contact with the skin or saliva of a person who has the infection, including vaginal, anal, or oral sex.\n\nTreatment for these conditions will vary depending on the specific infection and its severity.\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating herpes, HPV, and other STDs is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. This typically involves a physical exam, as well as blood tests, swabs, or other diagnostic tests to confirm the presence of the infection.\n\nStep 2: Antiviral Medications Antiviral medications can be effective for managing symptoms of herpes and other viral STDs. These medications work by blocking the replication of the virus, reducing the severity and duration of symptoms. Examples of antiviral medications used to treat herpes include acyclovir, valacyclovir, and famciclovir.\n\nStep 3: Topical Treatments Topical treatments can be used to manage symptoms of genital warts caused by HPV. These may include prescription creams or ointments, such as imiquimod or podophyllin, which work to destroy the warts by stimulating the immune system.\n\nStep 4: Surgery or Procedures In some cases, surgery or other procedures may be necessary to manage symptoms of STDs. For example, cryotherapy or laser therapy may be used to remove genital warts caused by HPV, while surgical excision may be necessary to remove lesions or sores caused by herpes.\n\nStep 5: Partner Notification and Testing If you are diagnosed with an STD, it\'s important to notify your sexual partners so that they can also be tested and treated if necessary. Your healthcare provider can help you develop a plan for partner notification and testing.\n\nStep 6: Prevention and Follow-Up Care Prevention is an important part of managing STDs. This may include practicing safe sex, getting vaccinated against HPV and other STDs, and getting regular STI screenings. After treatment, it\'s important to follow-up with your healthcare provider regularly to ensure that symptoms are improving and to prevent recurrence. Your provider may recommend ongoing treatment, screening, or other measures to manage the infection and prevent future complications.</string>
    <string name="Disease19">Seborrheic Keratoses</string>
    <string name="Disease19Description">Seborrheic keratoses are usually brown, black or light tan. The growths (lesions) look waxy or scaly and slightly raised. They appear gradually, usually on the face, neck, chest or back.Seborrheic keratoses are harmless and not contagious. \n\nTreatment for these conditions will depend on the location, size, and severity of the growth.\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating seborrheic keratoses and other benign tumors is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. This typically involves a physical exam, as well as a biopsy or other diagnostic tests to confirm the nature of the growth.\n\nStep 2: Observation In some cases, small or benign growths may not require treatment. Your healthcare provider may recommend simply observing the growth to ensure that it does not change or become problematic over time.\n\nStep 3: Cryotherapy Cryotherapy involves the use of extreme cold to freeze and destroy the growth. This may be a good option for small or superficial growths, particularly those located in areas that are difficult to treat with other methods.\n\nStep 4: Curettage and Electrodessication Curettage and electrodessication involve the use of a scalpel or curette to remove the growth, followed by the application of an electric current to stop bleeding and promote healing. This method is often used for larger or thicker growths.\n\nStep 5: Laser Therapy Laser therapy uses high-energy beams of light to destroy the growth. This method may be preferred for growths that are difficult to reach with other methods, or for growths located in highly visible areas.\n\nStep 6: Surgical Excision Surgical excision involves the use of a scalpel or other surgical instrument to remove the growth. This method is typically reserved for larger growths, or for those that are located in sensitive or difficult-to-treat areas.\n\nStep 7: Follow-Up Care After treatment, it\'s important to follow-up with your healthcare provider regularly to ensure that the growth has been fully removed and to monitor for any signs of recurrence. Your provider may recommend ongoing observation or additional treatment as needed.</string>
    <string name="Disease20">Actinic Keratosis Carcinoma</string>
    <string name="Disease20Description">Actinic keratoses (also called solar keratoses) are dry scaly patches of skin that have been damaged by the sun. The patches are not usually serious. But there\'s a small chance they could become skin cancer, so it\'s important to avoid further damage to your skin.\n\nEarly detection and treatment are critical for managing these conditions and reducing the risk of complications.\n\nStep 1: Accurate Diagnosis The first step in treating actinic keratosis, basal cell carcinoma, and other malignant lesions is to obtain an accurate diagnosis. This typically involves a physical exam, as well as a biopsy or other diagnostic tests to confirm the nature of the lesion.\n\nStep 2: Mohs Micrographic Surgery Mohs micrographic surgery is a highly effective technique for removing malignant lesions while preserving healthy tissue. This method involves the removal of thin layers of skin, which are examined under a microscope to ensure that all cancerous cells have been removed.\n\nStep 3: Excisional Surgery Excisional surgery involves the complete removal of the lesion, along with a margin of healthy tissue to ensure that all cancerous cells have been removed. This method is typically used for smaller lesions or those located in areas that are easily accessible.\n\nStep 4: Radiation Therapy Radiation therapy involves the use of high-energy radiation beams to destroy cancerous cells. This method may be used for larger or more advanced lesions, or for those that cannot be treated with surgery.\n\nStep 5: Topical Medications Topical medications, such as imiquimod or 5-fluorouracil, may be used to treat early-stage actinic keratosis or other pre-cancerous lesions. These medications work by stimulating the immune system to attack and destroy abnormal cells.\n\nStep 6: Photodynamic Therapy Photodynamic therapy involves the use of a topical medication and a special light source to destroy cancerous cells. This method is often used for early-stage lesions, or for those located in sensitive or difficult-to-treat areas.\n\nStep 7: Follow-Up Care After treatment, it\'s important to follow-up with your healthcare provider regularly to ensure that all cancerous cells have been removed and to monitor for any signs of recurrence. Your provider may recommend ongoing observation or additional treatment as needed. Additionally, it\'s important to practice good sun protection habits and avoid excessive sun exposure to reduce the risk of developing new lesions.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>


</resources>